#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/rob-parnell-b0aa558b (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Communication
Sports
Microsoft Office

Honors-Awards
Most Valuable Player
Vice Captain

# Rob Parnell

Employee Engagement Specialist United Kingdom

### Summary

As a senior sales development representative at Reward Gateway, I help businesses create a more engaged and productive workforce by offering employee engagement solutions. I have over four years of experience in sales and recruitment, working with clients across various industries and sectors. I have excellent communication and interpersonal skills, and I enjoy motivating and supporting my team to achieve our goals. I am passionate about employee engagement and wellbeing, and I believe in the mission and values of Reward Gateway. I am always looking for new opportunities to learn and grow in my field of expertise.

## Experience

Reward Gateway 3 years 9 months

Senior Employee Engagement Specialist March 2023 - Present (1 year 8 months) London, England, United Kingdom

Employee Engagement Specialist February 2021 - March 2023 (2 years 2 months) London, England, United Kingdom

Sanderson Recruitment PLC Consultant September 2019 - July 2020 (11 months) Reading, United Kingdom

Redundancy due to Covid-19

Venn Group
Associate Consultant
October 2018 - September 2019 (1 year)
Reading, United Kingdom

Pertemps Managed Solutions Recruitment Resourcer August 2018 - October 2018 (3 months)

Reading, United Kingdom

# Education

University of Reading History · (2016 - 2018)

St Columba's College, St Albans (2008 - 2015)